{
	"data": [
    {
      "question": "We _________ hardly believe it.",
      "a": "won't",
      "b": "ought",
      "c": "can't",
      "d": "can",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- Can hardly do something: something is not true or does not happen at all",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Can you play basketball?  \"I ___ play basketball.\"",
      "a": "am used to",
      "b": "am used for",
      "c": "used to",
      "d": "used of",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n\nRemember:\n\n- used to + V\n\n- be used to + V-ing",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "I was late again this morning. \"Well, I think you had better ___ on time.\"",
      "a": "start being",
      "b": "to start to be",
      "c": "started being",
      "d": "to be",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- Had better + V",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "I am sorry. I broke your g lasses. \" It ___ \"",
      "a": "matters not",
      "b": "has no matter",
      "c": "doesn't matter",
      "d": "isn't matter",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n\n- We use \"It doesn't matter\"",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": " Do you mind closing the window? \" ___. We have enough fresh air.",
      "a": "No, I don't mind",
      "b": "Yes, I don't",
      "c": "No, I do",
      "d": "No, I don't",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n\n- Do you mind ....? No, I don't.\n\n",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "I usually go dancing at night. \" ___ do that.\"",
      "a": "You had not better",
      "b": "You had better not",
      "c": "You had better not to",
      "d": "You have better not",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- Had better + V \n- Had better not + V",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "His advice ___ not be taken.",
      "a": "was needed",
      "b": "needs",
      "c": "need",
      "d": "is needed",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n\nRemember:\n\n- Need is also a modal verb: no ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you speak French ? \" No, I don't speak French, but I ___ speak Chinese.\"",
      "a": "do",
      "b": "must",
      "c": "ought",
      "d": "have to",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- S + do + V",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "John smokes too much. \" Well, he used to smoke more than he ___ now.\"",
      "a": "did",
      "b": "does",
      "c": "could",
      "d": "has",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- Now -&gt; does",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "___ you like to join us for supper?",
      "a": "Did",
      "b": "Don't",
      "c": "Will",
      "d": "Would",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- Would like + to + V",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    }
  ]
}